Stephanie Lane

Full-Stack Web Developer

I am passionate about problem-solving, making user-friendly websites, and collaborating with a team. I have professional experience mentoring, tutoring, and teaching others. Helping and collaborating with others are things which I love to do and feel would make me a valuable asset to the Adobe team.



stephlane544@gmail.com



520-286-0841



Salt Lake City, UT



www.stephanielane.tech

in

linkedin.com/in/stephanie--lane



@StephLane544



github.com/stephlane544

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern

Adobe

05/2019 - 08/2019

Lehi, UT

Marana, AZ

- Create a plugin for Kibana (a dashboard for data in ElasticSearch search engine)
- Get familiar with Kibana open source code base
- Determine and implement necessary code to create plugin

Teacher - 7th Grade Pre-Algebra

Marana Unified School District

07/2018 – 12/2018

- Created and delivered Pre-Algebra curriculum to 150 middle school students
- Provided mentorship after school to two low-income and low-performing girls

SKILLS

JavaScript









Node is

Mongoose



MongoDB



JSON

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Swap Meet - Link: https://swap-meet-for-freelancers.herokuapp.com/

- A website app for bartering services. Users create a profile with a service they can offer to others, which will then show up in the searched services. Users can search for others services, and can use the app to barter their services or can call/email the user directly for services.
- Built using: React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS

Noted - Link: https://noted-note-taking.herokuapp.com/

- Noted is an app for small notes, but it also has a collections section in which users can make a book with whatever content they would like.
- Built using: React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS

Triva Game - Link: https://stephanie_lane_TriviaGame.surge.sh

- Created a trivia game using opentdb API. It randomly gives a user a question, shows the correct and incorrect answers once an answer is chosen, and keeps track of the users score. In addition, the user can search through the questions for specific words, category, difficulty level, or type.
- Built using: HTML, CSS, and React

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Certification

V School

01/2019 − 04/2019

■ 12 week immersive program focusing on the MERN stack

Salt Lake City, UT

BA in Mathematics

University Of Arizona

05/2018 Tucson, Arizona